

□ (+61) 403280788 | **■** terryzhuo25@gmail.com | **□** terryyz | **□** terry-zhuo

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

## **Summary**

Current Computer Science Undergraduate at UNSW. Experience in digital signal processing, quantum computing and natural language processing. Research interests lie in question answering, language model and vision-language grounding. Super nerd who loves Python, C++ and Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_

#### **Monash Univeristy**

Melbourne, Victoria

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SUPERVISED BY REZA HAFFARI AND LIZHEN QU

May. 2020 - Present

- Working closely with PhD students in the team on several NLP projects.
- · Proposed a zero-shot question answering model that improves over the state-of-the-art QA models.
- Co-authored a long paper in COLING 2020.

# UNSW Sydney CASUAL ACADEMIC

Sydney, Australia
Feb. 2020 - Present

Teaching in ENGG1000: Introduction to Engineering Design and Innovation

• Teaching in ELEC2134: Circuits and Signals. The only undergraduate in the team while remains are PhDs.

#### Quantum Computation and Communication Technology (CQC2T), UNSW Sydney

Sydney, Australia

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY ARNE LAUCHT

Nov. 2019 - Sep. 2020

- Proposed a research project of digitizing the lock-in amplifier in MATLAB.
- · Proposed the implementation structure of the digitizing lock-in amplifier in the team's quantum computing system.

Microsoft Shanghai, China

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec. 2019 - Feb. 2020

- Applied Azure SQL DB/DW, Azure Data Lake Storage, Azure Data Lake Analytics, Azure Machine Learning, Stream Analytics, Azure Data Factory, or Cosmos DB to companies' data.
- · Designed cloud architecture for top tier companies.
- Strongly recommended by Michael Wang.

# **Project**

### Off-world Robotics Project, Vertically Integrated Project

UNSW Sydney

RESEARCHER

Feb. 2020 - Present

- Determineing the constraints of our embedded systems, sourcing embedded boards for use on the prototype rovers, and testing them with an RTOS or scheduling architecture.
- · Researching existing approaches to the SLAM problem, comparing them, and proposing a SLAM system for use on the rovers.

Py Googletrans Github

CONTRIBUTOR, COLLABORATOR

May. 2020 - Present

- · Star: 2.0k
- · Fork: 408
- · Googletrans: Free and Unlimited Google translate API for Python. Translates totally free of charge.

#### **Sphinx Markdown Builder**

Github

May. 2020 - Present

Contributor
• Star: 79

- · Fork: 28
- · Sphinx builder that outputs markdown files.

# **Education**

### **UNSW Sydney (University of New South Wales)**

Sydney, Australia

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (MINOR IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

Jul. 2018 - Sep. 2021(Expected)

• Weighed Average Mark 88.2, Top 2% in Faculty of Engineering

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

BLUESAT UNSW Sydney

Power EngineerWorking on the satellite project which will be launched in 2021-2022.

- Supervising in MPPT board testing and designing.
- Supervising in Mil 1 board testing and designing.

**ELSOC UNSW**UNSW Sydney

ACADEMIC TUTOR, SUB-COMMITTEE MEMBER

May. 2019 - Present

Oct. 2019 - Present

• Ran crashcourses (lectures) where more than twenty students on average attended.

### Publication \_\_\_\_\_

# COSMO: Conditional SEQ2SEQ-based Mixture Model for Zero-Shot Commonsense Question Answering

**COLING 2020** 

FARHAD MOGHIMIFAR, LIZHEN QU, YUE ZHUO, MAHSA BAKTASHMOTLAGH AND GHOLAMREZA HAFFARI

### Honors & Awards

2019	<b>Highly Commended Undergraduate</b> , Dean's Honours List   UNSW Engineering	Sydney, Australia
2019	Taste of Research Winner, Taste of Research Scholarships   UNSW Engineering	Sydney, Australia

### Service\_\_\_\_

2020	Volunteer, EMNLP 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, NeurIPS 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, WiNLP 2020	Seattle, WA